

IRYNA SKARAIEVA

Front-End Developer

I'm a Front-End Developer transitioning into IT after many years of working in education. My teaching experience has equipped me with strong analytical skills, problem-solving abilities, and teamwork capabilities. With a foundation in JavaScript, React and HTML/CSS, I focus on crafting functional, visually appealing web applications to enhance user experiences.

Proposals for cooperation with technologies that need to be studied are welcome!

CONTACT DETAILS

+421919495444

Trnava, Slovak Republic

LINKS TO OTHER RESOURCES

<u>Portfolio</u> <u>WhatsApp</u> <u>Telegram</u>

<u>Linkedin</u> <u>Facebook</u> <u>GitHub</u>

SKILLS

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

SCSS

React

Next.js

Figma

Bulma

Tailwind CSS

LANGUAGES

Ukrainian Native

Russian C2

English B1

Slovak B1

EDUCATION

The Faculty of Physics and Mathematics

Teacher of Physics, Computer Science and Life Safety Basics **Master's degree** Sep 2002 — June 2007

South Ukrainian National Pedagogical University named after K. D. Ushynsky

WORK EXPERIENCE

Teacher of Physics and Astronomy, Private Tutor

Self-Employed, Remote, UA, SK | Feb 2020 - Mar 2024 Medical College, Mykolayiv, UA | Jan 2014 - Aug 2015 Secondary School, Odesa, UA | Sep 2007 - Sep 2012

- \cdot Created educational materials, building skills in multimedia.
- · Developed instructional documentation.
- · Managed the educational process for a home-schooled student.
- · Supervised student groups.

Content Manager

Freelance, Vinnytsya, UA | Feb 2016 - May 2017

- · Editing and managing website content using the Content Management System.
- $\cdot \text{Strict compliance with requirements and deadlines}.$

Accountant

T&T, Mykolayiv, UA | Jan 2013 - Mar 2013

- \cdot Processed financial transactions with accuracy and attention to detail, managed large datasets, enhancing analytical skills.
- \cdot Adapted to new software, proving flexibility and fast learning.

DRIVING LICENSE
B